Could you stop the camera?
Excuse me?
Do it right now, or I'll break it.
U-Understood!
Hunter Sung. What do you
intend to do to Byung-gu?
I asked you a question!
We're running out of time.
Please stop talking.
Arise.
The chairman has called for the
execution of plan 9. Are you ready?
Are you insane?!
You wanna send us back to the island
while that monster is still there?!
You'd be singing a different tune
if you'd seen it yourself!
Goto died... like it was nothing.
The new variant is dead.
One of their hunters took it down.
It's... dead?
Do you still insist on staying behind?
A skill that lets you use
the powers of the dead?!
It wasn't just summoning magic?
Byung-gu...
I heard a voice.
It was Hunter Min, asking me to use his power.
I think I can tell what he was like in life.
To immediately go and heal Hunter Cha
without even being given the order...
He must've been a kind, caring person.
I can see why he wouldn't
want this getting out on TV.
The ability to grow stronger and stronger
as he engages in more difficult battles...
What a monstrous ability.
But with Min...
Hunter Sung.
If you intend to continue battling as a hunter,
I'm sure Byung-gu's power
will be of great use to you.
But... He always hated fighting.
I would rather he not have
to return to the battlefield.
This takes me back to the red gate incident.
You grabbed my shoulder then, too.
But this time, instead of giving an order,
you're making an earnest plea.
Don't worry. I was thinking the same thing.
Release extraction.
Thank you so much.
How are they alive?
After a rendezvous with Hunter Sung,
he proceeded to defeat the new variant.
I can see that, you fool!
How is he on the island?!
I thought he wasn't participating in the raid!
There's no way to tell.
From the magic power readings,
all we can say is he appeared out of nowhere.
This is a nightmare. And after we lost
seven of our ten S-Rank hunters!
Chairman, should we proceed with plan 9?
Any further casualties will undercut
our ability to respond to domestic gates,
to say nothing about
the global balance of power.
What's your call?
We're pulling out. Withdraw immediately.
Understood.
Why have the ants started
coming at us so suddenly?!
How should we know?!
I thought the queen was dead!
That's probably why!
With their leader gone, they're running amok!
We can't let them reach the mainland!
They ain't gettin' past us!
Time to show these bugs
what the Knights Guild can do!
You got it, Master!
Hurry, everyone!
Well, this is a real shitshow.
It seems like the ants trying to flee
the island are spreading out
and heading toward the mainland.
We have to hurry before
they cut off our route back!
We should take off at once. Let's go.
What about Hunter Sung?
He's staying behind to take care
of the remaining ants and eggs.
I hate to admit it, but in our condition,
we'd only slow him down.
And though she's no longer in mortal danger,
it'd be better to have the medic team
examine Hunter Cha as soon as possible.
Getting experience from smashing
unhatched eggs is a nice surprise.
I almost feel bad for not
using this thing more often.
The Demon Monarch's Sword
sure does live up to its name.
That said... I'll leave the rest to you guys.
I've finally hit level 100.
He's still emitting a ton of aura,
even after dying.
Arise.
What is this darkness? I can't sense anything.
Did something happen during the extraction?
I'm back.
For a second there, I thought it had failed.
Well, on to the other ants...
My king.
Did you just talk?
Yes.
None of the other shadows
could talk... So why can he?
My king, I ask that you grant me a name.
"General" rank? Never seen that before.
Is the new rank why he can talk?
And I've gotta wonder...
I was the one who killed you.
Are you still willing to obey me?
I did not die.
By your hand, I was reborn.
I am filled with joy.
I swear to serve you for eternity.
Please grant me a name.
Beru.
Your name is Beru.
I am honored.
Now, back to business.
Arise.
They got past the hunters at sea!
We're the last line of defense!
We cannot let them reach the cities!
Oh, no, no, no!
How the hell do we fight these things?!
Tanks, get in front!
We hold the line, or we die trying!
That's a lot of ants.
Four thousand without a leader.
They appear to be fleeing in all directions.
There were still that many?!
Can you thin out the numbers for me?
If that is your wish, my king, then certainly.
You need only say the word.
Go.
Good! Keep it up.
These things are dangerous,
so be careful and take one down at a time!
Work together, and make sure—
Mr. Song!
Are you okay, Mr. Song?!
What just happened?!
What was that light?
I don't know. But I think it saved us.
Jinwoo...
There's just too damn many!
Can't you do something?
Not without wrecking the helicopter, no!
I hate this.
There's not a lot we can do in midair.
In the end, he saved us once again.
They should be able to make it back now.
Afterward, the majority of the ants
that had dispersed from the island
were held off by the many hunters in the field,
minimizing the damage to the mainland.
Our country's S-Rank hunters returned safely.
Hunter Cha, who remained unconscious,
was transported to a hospital.
It was a battle with many casualties,
but the emergent threat from the island
was successfully dealt with.
And so, the fourth Jeju Island raid
ended in our victory.
Looks like we've got more
visitors from far abroad.
It's been two days of this now.
They'll be within firing range shortly.
Notify the mage-type hunters on standby.
Prepare to intercept.
No, belay that order.
Our country's hero
seems to want a bit of exercise.
Here they come.
Can't just sit around all day, after all.
Let's send every last one of them
to a watery grave.
If I'd gotten a crack at the black ant
instead of these peons,
I might've actually had some fun.
What a shame.
It's now been several days
since the raid ended.
A memorial has been erected
to honor the victims,
and a large crowd has
come to pay their respects.
Here we have the S-Rank hunter,
Sung Jinwoo, approaching the table.
He contributed a great deal to this raid,
with some saying that it would not have been
a success without his participation.
Some are calling him a hero...
But at the same time, many are
questioning whether or not
there would have been fewer casualties
had he participated from the start,
to sum up some of the more critical voices.
Please hold your head high.
No matter what the public thinks, you're
the one who put an end to this tragedy.
As chairman of the Hunter's Association,
I'd like to first thank you
for your service during
the fourth Jeju Island raid.
No... If I had got there sooner,
maybe Hunter Min could have survived.
But thanks to you, the other five S-Ranks and
many of our countrymen's lives were saved.
That is a major accomplishment.
I promise that you will be rewarded
however you wish in due time.
I understand.
Now, I was wondering what
your plans are for the future.
The future, sir?
Right.
This raid resulted in your power being
demonstrated on an international level.
I doubt the public will leave you alone.
There will be many who will
try to approach you, as well.
The Association can't ignore that.
Which is why I feel the need
to ask you, Hunter Sung...
What do you intend to do
with your great power, and where?
I'm thinking about starting my own guild.
How the hell didya end up
stuck on cleanup duty
instead of attendin' the
memorial service, Master?!
Hey, dumbass. Makin' sure the
enemies're dead, killin' stragglers,
and collectin' resources is all important stuff.
Bein' entrusted with the last bits
of a job is a sign they trust me.
But...
And besides...
A real man does the job he's given,
nice and steady, without no bitchin'.
You're so awesome, Master!
Who the hell're you?!
This place is off-limits!
What are you doing—
What was that?!
I dunno who you are,
but yer not supposed—
What did you do?
All the noise they were making
was bothering me.
I just had them take a little nap.
So, were you able to make sure?
Yeah. It was definitely his power.
So very strange.
Someone like that, helping humans...
He's always been an odd one.
If you're that curious, go and see him.
If the opportunity presents itself.
I think we're done here.
Let's head back.
Isn't one of them here?
We can leave this area to him.
In other words,
you don't want to get involved.
The hunt will commence as planned.
That hasn't changed.
I guess it's not worth the extra trouble.
Quite the stench, though. I can only imagine
the fuss she'd make if she were here.
I'm not getting anywhere.
So, about the guild...
Oh, Chairman Go just gave his approval.
Seriously?! Then I'll get
right on finding us an office!
Hey!
Wait—
Jinwoo! Make sure you hire me, okay?!
I promise I'll be useful!
Come on, we're discussing
some very important—
I'm hanging up.
Like what, exactly?
Those two...
Man, I am seriously not getting anywhere.
Hello?
Hunter Sung. This is Go.
Did something happen with the guild?
No, I'm calling about something else.
Further down this highway?
Correct. A B-Rank gate has appeared.
That explains it.
Hunters are being arranged for,
but it's going to take some time
before they can get there.
Well, if you don't mind...
One vehicle at a time, please!
How much longer before the hunters get here?
You mean the traffic's so bad
the hunters can't make it?!
What are we supposed to do?
Hey, don't hang up!
I'm here to close the gate.
Oh, right!
Manager Woo informed me.
But it's going to be a while before
the other hunters are able to make it—
I'll be fine solo.
But...
There he goes.
I mean, I know it's only a B-Rank gate, but...
Don't tell me...
Well, this is obviously a red gate.
How does this keep happening to me?
The exit's closed, and I have no idea
how far this forest extends...
Now I'm thinking I should've
told Mom I was gonna be late.
Then again, if this is all that's in here,
it shouldn't take that long.
Let's make this quick.
He came to the memorial ceremony.
This raid proved that
I still have a lot to learn.
I wasn't able to do anything.
I had to be saved.
But not him.
I want to catch up to him.
I want to stand at his side.
And to do that...
I need to get stronger.
Hunters are born to hunt.
Dungeons are worlds
where survival is all that matters,
and a hunter has to be prepared
to become prey at any time.
That's because there's no telling
when the roles might be reversed.
You're always one step away from death.
But hunters are still willing to fight,
no matter how many enemies they face,
or how much stronger those enemies might be.
They've all got different
reasons for fighting.
To protect their family.
To uphold their ideals.
To prove who they are.
To defy fate.
So hunters continue to hunt.
And none of them are ready to stop.
On to the next target.